http://hudsonfasteners.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
PRIVACY POLICY
By using the Web site (the “Site”) provided by Hudson Fasteners (“Hudson”), you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information, including your personally identifiable information, by Hudson in accordance with the terms of our Privacy Policy in effect at that time. Please also see our Site’s Terms of Use and Return Policy for other terms and conditions governing your use of the Site. You acknowledge that we have the right, at our sole discretion, to modify any terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy without prior notice to you. Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately following the posting of such changes on our Site. For this reason, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy on a periodic basis.
User Registration and Other Transactions
You may visit the Site without disclosing any personally identifiable information. You may, however, voluntarily provide personally identifiable contact information through our Site, for example, by registering with our Site. During registration, you will be asked to supply personally identifiable information that may include your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. The primary reasons that we collect personally identifiable information are to contact you, provide you with information, newsletters and materials, respond to your requests and questions, provide you with information about special product offers and new products, and to better understand the use of our Site.
Usage Tracking Hudson may track user traffic patterns throughout the Site. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to users’ needs and helps us understand the demographics of our audience.
Cookies Hudson may use cookies. A cookie is a small data file that some sites attach to users’ hard drives when they visit the sites. A cookie file can contain information that the Site uses to track the pages users have visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain has to be supplied by the user. Hudson may use cookies to track user traffic patterns.
Disclosure of Information
Hudson may share your personally identifiable information or aggregate information with affiliates, business partners, third parties performing functions on our behalf, and/or a third party that acquires ownership or control of our business. We may also disclose information if we believe in good faith that is required by law.
Information, suggestions, and comments received by Hudson will be deemed to be non-confidential. Hudson will be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such information to others without limitation. Further, Hudson will be free to use any ideas and concepts contained in such information for any purpose whatsoever.
Third Party Sites
This Privacy Policy only applies to this Site. Should this Site refer to or link to Sites outside the control of Hudson, please be aware that these Sites may collect personal information about you, and that they operate according to their own privacy practices, which may differ from our Privacy Policy.
Opt-Out Policy
Users may choose not to register with this Site. If you wish to stop receiving certain types of information from us, please send an email to info@hudsonfasteners.com.
Security Precautions
The transmission of information over the Internet or other publicly accessible networks is not secure, and is subject to possible loss, interception or alteration while in transit. Accordingly, we do not assume any liability for any damage you may experience or costs you may incur as a result of any transmissions over the Internet or other publicly accessible networks, such as the submission of any of your personally identifiable information to us.
Use by Children
We do not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children through our Site. Individuals under eighteen (18) should consult with a parent or guardian about the use of this Site.
Updating Information; Questions
Any user who desires to review, amend or correct information relating to them, or has questions about personal information submitted to Hudson, should contact us at info@ hudsonfasteners.com.
Connect with us
FacebookTwitterPinterestYouTubeLinkedIn
Newsletter
Name
Email
Our Story
Contact Us
Fastener News Desk
All prices are in USD.
